{
    "cloze": [
    {
        "question": "Randall Cunningham was Quarterback for the Vikings team that went 15-1 during the 1998 season.",
        "answer": "Randall Cunningham"
    },
    {
        "question": "Freddie Mitchell caught the famous 4 and 26 play against the Packers.",
        "answer": "Freddie Mitchell"
    },
    {
        "question": "Donovan McNabb was the Quarterback of the Eagles during their last trip to the Super Bowl.",
        "answer": "Donovan McNabb"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Philadelphia Eagles beat Vince Lombardi's Packers during the 1960 championship.",
        "answer": "Philadelphia Eagles"
    },

    {
        "question": "The Eagles beat the Dallas Cowboys to advance to their first Super Bowl",
        "answer": "Dallas Cowboys"
    }
   ],
    "basic": [
    {
        "question": "The martial art of kung fu originated in which country?",
        "answer": "China"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the United States, where can alligators and crocodiles be found together in the wild?",
        "answer": "South Florida"
    },
    {
        "question": "What famous female singer died of alcohol poisoning in 2011 at the age of 27?",
        "answer": "Amy Winehouse"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the popular Christmas song, Frosty the Snowman, what are the snowman's eyes made out of?",
        "answer": "Coal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the author of 'The Amityville Horror' published in 1977?",
        "answer": "Jay Anson"
    }]
}